PABLO MARTIN, LOPEZ



About me

I want to acquire experience and skills that allow me to grow and continue developing knowledge. Manage to face new challenges by demonstrating my potential, in order to achieve proposed goals in the medium and long term.



+54 1165428432



pablo_mtv08@hotmail.com



Argentina - Buenos Aires

Age: 29

LANGUAGES

- Native Spanish
- Intermediate English

NETWORKS/WEB



github.com/pabloApoca



linkedin.com/in/pablo-martin-lopez/



pabloapoca.github.io/mi-portfolio/

OPERATING SYSTEMS

100 %
LINUX 50 %

Full Stack Developer

EXPERIENCE

TECNOSOFTWARE

Jan 2024 - Present

Ssr Software Developer at Prisma Medios de Pagos

I work on the development of Software for banking systems regarding Banelco ATMs.

Technologies: Html / Css / Tailwind CSS / Bootstrap / Javascript / Git-Bitbucket / Jira / Scrum / Teams.

OverVision Analytics Full Stack Developer

Apr 2022 - Oct 2023

Development of Desktop and Mobile applications.

Technologies: PHP / Laravel 9, VueJs 3 / Html / Css / Tailwind CSS / Javascript, Databases PostgreSQL, Git-GitLab y Jira.

Digital House

Mar 2021- Jul 2023

Programming Teacher

- Mar 2021 Apr 2022 (FULLTIME): Teaching Backend programming classes in Mercadolibre and Globant Bootcamps, technologies: Git, Java +11, Golang, Api/Rest Spring Boot, Testing, Databases SQL/NoSQL and Scrum methodology.
- <u>Apr 2022 Jul 2023 (PART TIME)</u>: Technical Assistant and content designer in the Digital House career, Certified Tech Developer, together with <u>Mercadolibre</u> and <u>Globant</u> participating in the second year with the Java programming language and third year in Golang.

Certant

Oct 2020 - Mar 2021

Full Stack Developer

Requirements analysis, Software development in Java programming language, web development with Angular Javascript Framework and developing SQL queries in MySQL.

EDUCATION

School of Technical Education N° 3 - Claypole

2009 - 2011

- Bachelor's Degree in Production of Goods and Services.
- Senior Master of Works.

Databases SQL/noSQL

National University of Lanús - UNLA

2012-2021

Career: Bachelor's degree in systems

- University Programmer Analyst (Completed).
- Bachelor's degree in systems (In progress, I only need the Thesis)

80 %

WORK TOOLS

VueJs 3 95 %

API REST 100 %

Jira 70 %

靐

PABLO MARTIN, LOPEZ



Sobre mi

Deseo adquirir experiencia y aptitudes que me permitan crecer y seguir desarrollando conocimientos. Lograr enfrentar nuevos desafíos demostrando mi potencial, con el fin de alcanzar metas propuestas a mediano y largo plazo.



+54 1165428432



pablo_mtv08@hotmail.com



Buenos Aires - Argentina

Edad: 29

IDIOMAS

- Español (Nativo)
- Ingles (Intermedio)

REDES/WEB



github.com/pabloApoca



linkedin.com/in/pablo-martin-lopez/



pabloapoca.github.io/mi-portfolio/

SISTEMAS OPERATIVOS

100 %
LINUX 50 %

Desarrollador Full Stack

EXPERIENCIA

TECNOSOFTWARE

Ene 2024 - Actualidad

Ssr Software Developer en Prisma Medios de Pagos

Trabajo en el desarrollo de Software para los sistemas bancarios con respecto a los cajeros Banelco.

Tecnologías: Html / Css / Tailwind CSS / Bootstrap / Javascript / Git-Bitbucket / Jira / Scrum / Teams.

OverVision Analytics Desarrollador Full Stack

Abr 2022 - Oct 2023

Desarrollo de aplicaciones de Escritorio y Mobile.

Tecnologías: PHP / Laravel 9, VueJs 3 / Html / Css / Tailwind CSS /

Javascript, Base de datos PostgreSQL, Git-GitLab y Jira.

Digital House

Mar 2021- Jul 2023

Profesor de Programación

- Mar 2021 Abr 2022 (FULLTIME): Dictado de clases de programación Backend en Bootcamps de Mercadolibre y Globant, tecnologías: Git, Java +11, Golang, Api/Rest Spring Boot, Testing, Bases de datos SQL/NoSQL y metodología Scrum.
- <u>Abr 2022 Jul 2023 (PART TIME)</u>: Asistente Técnico y contenidista en la carrera de Digital House, Certified Tech Developer, junto a <u>Mercadolibre y Globant participando en el segundo año con el</u> lenguaje de programación Java y tercer año en Golang.

Certant

Oct 2020 - Mar 2021

Desarrollador Full Stack

Análisis de requerimientos, desarrollo de Software en lenguaje de programación Java, desarrollo web con Framework de Javascript Angular y desarrollar queries sql en MySQL.

FORMACIÓN

Escuela de Educación Técnica N° 3 - Claypole

2009 - 2011

- Bachillerato en Producción de Bienes y Servicios
- Técnico Maestro Mayor de Obras.

Universidad Nacional de Lanús - UNLA

2012-2021

Carrera: Licenciatura en sistemas

- Analista Programador Universitario (Completado).
- Licenciatura en sistemas (En curso, solo me falta la Tesis).

HERRAMIENTAS DE TRABAJO

 Java
 85 %

 Angular
 80 %

 VueJs 3
 95 %

 API REST
 100 %

Base de datos SQL/noSQL 80 %

Jira — 70 %